Northpole is a tv movie, fantasy, family film directed by Douglas Barr.
Northpole, the magical city where Santa and his
elves live and work is in trouble.
Families around the globe have gotten too busy to enjoy the season together, and
Northpole depends on their holiday happiness to keep running.
In the hopes of turning things around, a determined young elf
befriends a little boy with a lot of spirit.
His skeptical journalist mom doesn’t have room in her heart for anything but the facts, so it’s going to take a little nudge from his charming
teacher to create an unbeatable Christmas team to turn around this town and share the importance of the season with the whole world.
Chelsea, played by Tiffani-Amber Thiessen.
Ryan, played by Josh Hopkins.
Kevin, played by Max Charles.
Clementine, played by Bailee Madison.
Josephine, played by Candice Glover.
Santa Claus, played by Robert Wagner.
Northpole is a 2014 American-Canadian Christmas fantasy
television film directed by Douglas Barr.
It premiered on the Hallmark Channel on November 15, 2014, and stars
Tiffani Thiessen, Josh Hopkins, Bailee Madison and Max Charles.
The film was followed by a sequel, Northpole: Open for
Christmas, released in November 2015.
Bailee Madison returned to play Clementine the Elf while the lead
pair was played by Lori Loughlin and Dermot Mulroney.
The film explores themes of elves, magic, santa
claus, north pole, christmas spirit.